Now we have to test this. Let's go back to
test provider once more. It'll be helpful to parameterize our tests
a little bit more, both for location and for date.
All right, now that we've parameterized our tests, let's go back
at looking into our insert read provider. For the weather,
we're currently using the raw content URI to query. But we
can also query on additional data. By cutting and pasting
this text, we can try the text with different query parameters.
We'll close the cursor because it's good
practice. Now for our second weather query,
we're going to test the first of
our new URIs: WeatherEntry.buildweatherlocation and we can use
our new task location parameter. Alright, let's
try running this test. And our test
passed. Alright. We're going to add one more
test with a slight variation on the query
using build weather location with start
date, instead. So, we're going to use test
location as well as test date. And now, let's run those tests. And
our tests pass. Now, sometimes it's
useful to actually demonstrate a test failure.
Let's put in a date that's certainly going to fail, 20150624. We would
expect this test to fail. Let's try it and indeed it fails. So
we're pretty sure that our tests are actually doing what we expect them to.